I feel like I can do anything right now.
I'm really really excited, Yuki-chan!
Sumomo, there it is! The star drop!
Yes!
It happened in the town closest to the stars.
A very treasured story that only the two of them knew.
Now, where should I begin first?
The story started after school one day, in the month of May.
I was taking my time thinking about the things I was told.
Hey Tsuwabuki, I know you're bad at socializing...
Can't you try getting along better with everyone in class?
Even if you say that...
What should I do?
Umm...
That was the start of everything.
At that time, she had just transferred so I couldn't even remember her last name.
It's cold.
Y-You're all wet.
S-Sorry...
Umm...
What happened, Sumomo? Are you crying?
I will never forgive someone who makes Sumomo cry!
Nako-chan, wait!
Well, well...
Oh my, what an interesting combination.
Akihime-san is close to tears, Yaeno-san is angry and Tsuwabuki-kun is here too.
That's because he made Sumomo cry.
That's not it, Nako-chan.
Tsuwabuki-kun didn't do anything wrong.
S-Sorry. I'm sorry!
Sumomo?
It's fine.
It's alright, so...
Hmm... I see!
Well then, perfect timing.
Perfect timing?
Anyway, one of the basics of gardening is pulling out the weeds.
This way, the sweet smelling May flowers are taken care of...
Doing this gives you a nice feeling, doesn't it?
Not that!
Kisaragi-sensei, why did it come to this?
Well, the Gardening Club only has two members. Akihime-san and Yaeno-san.
That's right. Yaeno-san, can you hand that thing to Tsuwabuki-kun?
Yes.
Hey...
You just came at the right time when we needed more people.
Don't tell me...
You are going to use this to lure me over to the Gardening Club?
Just as expected, Tsuwabuki-kun. Good decision.
Well then, I'll leave everything to you, the only male member.
See ya.
See ya... what?
Tsuwabuki, here.
The sprinkler framework.
Tsuwabuki-kun, we've been in the new class for more than a month now...
Excluding us, you've never talked to anyone else before, right?
Everyone is worried, you know.
Are you even listening, Tsuwabuki?
About just now, Nako-chan...
I dropped the watering pot when I bumped into him.
Then I got surprised at Tsuwabuki-kun getting wet. And then, and then...
I understand, Sumomo.
Really?
Thank goodness, Nako-chan.
Wah, it's finished. This is great, really great, right?
Yeah.
He really did it.
So where is Tsuwabuki now?
I guess being in the Gardening Club's pretty tough too.
It would be hard for just two girls.
Eh, so I'll be a Gardening Club member, just like that?
H-Hey you!
Step aside, please step aside!
I'm really sorry.
Are you hurt anywhere?
I'm fine but...
Are those ears?
Uwah!
Err... this is cosplay, yes just cosplay.
Cos... what?
Here, I believe this is yours.
I'll return it to you.
Now, please excuse me!
What was that all about?
Huh? What? Hey, what the...?!
Wah, this is so cute.
Why is it here?
Did someone forget it here or was it thrown away?
I feel bad for you.
What, what is this?
You don't have to worry, alright?
Huh, Akihime?
I'll bring you home.
Eh? W-What?
What a cute little doll.
Sumomo, is Tsuwabuki here?
No, I didn't see him anywhere.
Wait for a moment, okay?
I'm looking for a friend named Tsuwabuki-kun.
I'll be back soon.
No, I'm right here.
Is this a dream? What the hell is happening?
"What the hell is happening?" indeed.
K-Kisaragi-sensei!
To think that the one who would receive the fate of the stars is this mysterious.
W-Wait a second!
What are you going to do?
You don't have to worry, Tsuwabuki-kun.
That's easy for you to say...
Here, it won't hurt so...
Uwahh!
W-W-Wait a second...!
There you go.
Now you should be able to talk and move normally.
Ah!
You're right. I can speak!
I can move!
So, Tsuwabuki-kun...
You must have drank a juice that was dropped from somewhere, didn't you?
Huh? I wouldn't do such a thing...
Wait... Just now, I bumped into a weird guy and then...
That's it.
That must be the reason why you transformed.
That guy is someone from Figurare.
Figu- what?
Figu-ra-re. It is another world different than our world of Retroscena.
And in that world, transformation is a normal phenomenon.
Transformation.
Right.
Which means you drank the Figurare traveler's transformation potion.
Do you understand...?
Guess not.
Of course not!
There's no way I'd believe that Figura-whatever...
Come in.
Excuse me.
Kisaragi-sensei, we couldn’t find Tsuwabuki-kun anywhere.
Oh, he said he had some business to do so he went home earlier.
I see.
Looking for him about something?
Yeah. He finished setting up the sprinkler so we wanted to say thanks.
And there was a little misunderstanding earlier, so...
Why don't you do that tomorrow then?
It's getting dark now, so you both should head back too.
Okay.
Umm, did you see a doll? A cute little sheep.
Hmm, I don't think so.
I see. Goodbye.
Well then, I'll tell you how to return to your old self.
Huh? I can return to my old self? Really?
Of course.
However, a sheep like you wouldn't be able to do it.
I wonder what kind of destiny is waiting for you.
Today, I talked a lot with Tsuwabuki-kun.
It's Doll-chan!
Thank goodness, I thought I'd never see you again.
What a strange doll.
This is...?
Why? Why did it have to be Akihime?
It looks like a letter.
Maybe it got stuck.
Tsuwabuki-kun, I'm going to tell you how to return to your old self so...
you can tell your soon-to-be-chosen girl partner about it.
To begin with, this town is said to be the town nearest...
Now, Tsuwabuki-kun.
That ring will bring you to the chosen girl.
Hey, wait!
I will send you to your Stellar Spinear.
Have a nice trip!
Wait! Wait a second!
Why? Why did the girl have to be Akihime?
Hmm... "I'm a special doll."
"Due to certain circumstances, I cannot go back to my home."
"For me to return to the doll land,
I will need your power."
"If it's fine with you,
please take care of and help save me."
What's that supposed to mean?
It talked, and it's moving too.
Yay! This is great!
It really is a special Doll-chan.
I'm Akihime Sumomo. What is your name?
Tsuwa-
Tsuwabuki-kun.
In order for you to change back, you mustn't tell anybody your real identity.
If someone finds out...
None, I have no name!
Is that so?
Yes.
That was really close.
If my identity is known, I won't be able to return to my old self.
Umm, hey, what's the matter?
I'm sorry.
Not having a name...
There must be a reason to it, right?
I know! You're white, small and light, so... Yuki-chan.
From now on, you'll be Yuki-chan.
So I'm Yuki-chan, huh?
Note:"Ore" is considered a more manly and commanding way of referring to one's self as opposed to "Boku".
Hey, not 'Ore' but 'Boku' right?
Just because you can't go home, you shouldn't act wild.
Act wild?
Yuki-chan.
I'll do my best...
So you can go back home.
T-That's fine with you?
Well, you need my help right?
So what should I do?
Well, for me to return...
Use 'Boku'!
For me to return...
There are seven star drops.
Star drops?
The star drops can only be gathered by the chosen girl.
And that's me?
Looks like it.
So, I'm the chosen girl.
What would happen if I fail...?
No, I must let Yuki-chan go back home.
I'll do my best, Yuki-chan.
Thank you.
Akihime... she looks so different compared to when she's at school...
Huh? That's right, the ring.
A ring?
Wow! This is great!
When a star drop falls down, the ring will shine towards it.
Guess it's real.
Let's go, Yuki-chan.
Hold on tight so you don't fall off, okay?
Umm...
Use the ring!
Oh, right!
So that is a star drop?
It's going to drop near my school.
I wonder where it dropped at, Yuki-chan.
Umm...
Oh yeah! The star drop likes to drop somewhere that has pretty water.
Water?
It should be here.
But what's happening here?
This fountain's supposed to be old and there shouldn't be water flowing out of it anymore.
So that is the drop.
But that looks deep.
It isn't supposed to be this deep. I can't reach it.
Yay, this is great!
It's so great, so great!
It's just like magic!
If you don't hurry, the star drop will melt into the water!
Oh no!
I can't reach it at all, Yuki-chan.
That's right, words!
It's because we're not reading the detachment words.
What... are these...
...characters?
This part shows the Japanese characters.
Those blue characters are...
That's... 'pu'!
Next is 'ru'... 'vu'...
And then...
I think that's 'ra'.
Eh?
And then 'de', 'i', no... it's a small 'i'.
Pu-ru-vu Ra-di!
We have to catch up to it!
Wait!
Are you okay?
I was worried that I'd step on the flowers, so I fell.
I see.
The star drop...
Huh?
Where did...?
The star drop disappeared.
I'm sorry, Yuki-chan.
I'm not...
Well, umm... it likes water so how about spraying some water?
Use the sprinkler that we built today!
Today?
Whoops...
I see, that sprinkler!
There it is!
Wow, it's pretty!
Alright, this time I'll do it!
But it didn't work too well even with the words, right?
It must be because I was trying to get it from a difficult place.
Let's go, Yuki-chan!
Puruvu Radi!
We did it.
Yes.
So pretty.
Put it inside the glass flask we brought.
Okay.
Done.
Yay!
We did it, Yuki-chan!
Miss, that girl must be her...
Prima Palm, the one that will get in our way...
I won't hand over the star drops.
That was fun.
That was my first time doing something so fun and mysterious.
My heart was beating so fast.
Beating so fast...
But Yuki-chan, how did you know about the sprinkler that Tsuwabuki-kun built today...?
That's because... umm... err...
I...
The girl's name was Akihime Sumomo.
And now, there were six star drops left.
Speaking of rainy day memories...
You'd remember the person you shared an umbrella with.
Ah, who is that?
Who? Umm...
Guess it's nobody.
Ah... it's someone I admire.
Hey, I want to share an umbrella with someone cute like Sumomo.
Ahh. Well, that is...
...impossible for you.